One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
♪ Sniper Island's favorite son, ♪
そげきーの島でー
♪ evildoers better run... ♪
生まれたおーれーは
♪ My aim is always true! ♪
100ぱーつ　100ちゅー
♪ Lulu lala lu... ♪
ルルララルー
What the hell is he doing?
ねずみの目玉もロックオン！！
♪ Turning mice eyes into bull's-eyes, lock on! ♪
何やってんだあいつ？
Well, look at it from his perspective.
まあ 気持ちをくんでやれよ
♪ Your heart's in my sights, gotcha! Lock on! ♪
お前のハートもロックオン！！
He's unable to face her as a friend,
仲間として正面から助けに行ってやれねえ
so this is his own way of settling things.
あの野郎なりのケジメなのさ
♪ Sniper Island's hometown hero, ♪ ♪ he'll never back down! ♪
そげきーの島から来た男ー
What a pain in the ass...
面倒くせえ性分だなあ
Hey! Get over here!
おい！こっち来い！
Ah, alright.
あっ　はい
Okay, let's commence Operation Rescue Robin.
よし じゃあロビンちゃん奪回作戦を決行する
We're newly acquainted. Is there anything you wish to know about me?
君たち　初対面の私に 何か質問などないのかね？
First things first, you guys came from car six, so there are five cars left.
まず　お前らがいたのは第６車両 残る車両はあと５つ
You know, like, "Where is Sniper Island?"
“そげきの島ってどこにあるの？”とか
Robin is in one of those cars.
そのどれかにロビンちゃんはいる
Why, it's in your heart!
それはね　君の心の中さ
By the way, are you strong?
時におめえ　強えのか？
I'm super strong, jackass!
スーパー強えぞ　バカ野郎
Especially this week!
今週の俺は特に強え！
If we manage to rescue Robin, our mission's accomplished, but...
最終的には ロビンちゃんを救出できれば勝ちだが…
there's a lot of enemies.
敵は多い
If we're careless and get surrounded in these tight quarters, we're screwed.
下手に先走って 狭い列車の中で囲まれちまうとやっかいだ
Our best bet is to avoid the nobodies and take out their strongest fighters one by one.
無駄な戦いは極力省いて 順序よく主力を潰していったほうが得策だろう
Got it? Listen up...
いいか　よく聞け
Okay! Now I'm ready for battle!
よし！戦闘準備バッチリよ！
What's wrong?
何してんの？
What do you mean "what's wrong"?!
何してんのじゃねえ！
What are you doing changing out in the open?! You damn hussy!
てめえ　何堂々と ここで着替えてんだ　ハレンチ女！
– We don't mind.
–　ナイスハレンチ
What was I supposed to do? There's only one car.
しかたないじゃない １車両しかないんだもん
Cover your midriff! Put some pants on!
腹を隠せ！腹と脚を！
You too, Square Sisters!
おめえらもだ　スクエア！
People like you are corrupting society!
お前らみたいなのが 乱れた社会を作るんだ！
Shut up, bashful boy.
うるさいわいなてれ屋
Bashful boy.
てれ屋
Why you...!
このっ…
Dammit!
クソッ　ん
What's the point of even making pants' pockets this small?
この黒ズボン どうせポケット付きならもっとでっけえほうが
Don't stuff meat in your pockets!
肉を詰めるなポケットに！
You guys seem refreshed.
気分一新らねおめえら
And you look to be raring to go.
やる気満々じゃねえか
Of course!
当たり前だ！
We're doing this to save Robin!
ロビンを助けるためだからな
We'll knock them all out this time! Count on it!
あいつら 今度こそ全員ぶっ飛ばしてやる
You'd better!
当然でしょ
If you get stuck somewhere again, I'm not gonna forgive you!
またどっかに挟まったりしたら 許さないからね！
I'll be fine!
大丈夫！
I've got a reason to win now!
今度は絶対負けねえ理由があるんだ
A reason...
理由って…
Nami, did you change your weapon?
ナミ！お前武器変えたのか？
Not exactly.
ううん
After we got back from the sky island, Usopp upgraded it using dials.
これは空島から帰った後 ウソップがダイアルを使ってより強く改良してくれたの
It's the Perfect Climate Baton.
パーフェクトクリマ･タクトよ
I see. So it's Usopp's...
そうか　ウソップの…
That's right! It's Usopp's...
そう　ウソップの…
last... work.
そう　遺作…
Quit bringing the mood down!
しんみりさすな！
Ready?
いいか…
Alright, move.
じゃあ行くぞ
An intruder?
侵入者か…
Y-Yes, sir. That's what I heard.
は…　はい そういう証言で…
It's impossible to board Puffing Tom while it's running.
このパッフィングトム途中乗船は不可能
If there really is an intruder,
侵入者がいたとすれば
it means they snuck aboard before we departed.
出港から乗せちまってたことになるな
What a farce.
あきれたもんだ
I agree. It's a massive blunder.
おっしゃるとおりで… 面目ない
It goes both ways, however. They can't get off while it's running.
だが同時に 途中下船も不可能だ
Therefore, the intruder and criminals must still be on the train.
侵入者も罪人たちも 必ずまだこの海列車に乗ってる
Keep calm and find them.
落ち着いて捜せ
Y-Yes, sir!
–　はっ！
Captain T-Bone...
Ｔボーン大佐
Hiding in a small place like this would be hard.
この狭い車両内に隠れるなんて…
– Good evening!
–　こんばんは！
– There they are!
–　いたーっ！
They're behind the door!
扉の向こうだ！
We've found the criminals and a suspicious man!
罪人を含む 不審者３名発見！
They're in car seven! Corner and capture them!
第７車両にいたぞ！ 追い込んで捕らえろ！
You sure are lousy with a hammer.
なってねえなあ　ハンマー使いが…
Sh-Shut up!
うっ　うるせえ！
Stop this futile resistance!
悪あがきはやめろ！
Open the door!
扉を開けるんだ！
Board it up! Quickly!
早く閉じろ！
W-Will do.
あっわ…　分かってる
Marines, this way!
みんなこっちだ！
Suspicious men spotted in car seven!
第７車両で不審者を発見した
You found them?!
いたか！？
Alert car three, as well!
第３車両のヤツらにも伝えろ
Capture Franky alive! There's no escape, so corner them and bring them in cautiously!
追い込んで罪人フランキーは生け捕りにするんだ 逃げ場はない　慎重に拿捕せよ！
Hey! Stay back!
おい！下がってろ！
Whoa! They're shooting now!
うわっ！撃ってきた！
Any day now, Soge!
急げそげ！
Well, a little help would be nice!
いやおめえも手伝えよ！
Don't shoot blindly!
やたらと撃つなよ
We can't kill them!
殺しはまずい！
Dammit!
クソッ
Captain T-Bone...
Ｔボーン大佐
Step aside.
どいていなさい
I detest crooked swordplay.
曲がった太刀筋大嫌い
Right-Angle Flash...
直角閃光！
Bone Soir!
ボーンソワール！
Th-They're not here!
い…　いない！？
Above us?!
上か！
Hurry! The criminals are at the end of the train!
急げ！敵は最後尾だ
Now! Hurry!
今だ　急げ！
Don't tell me...
まさか…
Everyone, return to the front cars!
全員前方車両へ引き返せ！
It's a trap!
これはワナだ！
– A trap?!
–　ワナ！？
What the...?!
ん？何だ？
Go back! We've been had!
引き返せ！ワナだ！
What?!
何！？
Even if we want to go back, the door is...
引き返そうにも　ドアが…
Who was that?!
誰だ！？
The cars are detached!
切り離されてる～っ！
– What?!
–　何～っ！？
Dammit! They did this!
ちくしょう！あいつらだ！
Criminal scum! You'll regret this!
てめえら覚えてろ～っ！
So it was too late...
遅かったか…
Well then, gentlemen!
そんじゃ皆さん
Watch out for sea kings!
海王類にお気をつけて
Have a nice trip!
よい旅を！
Take care!
達者でな～っ！
Two cars' worth...
２車両分…
That's at least fifty small fries off the table.
これでざっと50人は雑魚が減ったろ
But, Sir Sanji...
しかしサンジ君
Aren't Straw Hat Luffy and the others coming along the same railway?
同じ線路上を麦わらのルフィ君たちが 通ってくるんじゃないかね？
Well, they'll figure something out.
まあ　何とかするだろ
Y-You bastards!
こ…　この野郎！
I'll blow you away with the door!
ドアごと吹き飛べ！
Oh, going somewhere?
おっ　外出ですか？
What?!
ええ～っ！？
Alright, shall we handle the other five cars?
よし　やるか　残り５両
Y-You son of a bitch!
てっ…　てめえ
Don't think you can get away with this!
ただで済むと思うなよ！
How dare you?! Even Captain T-Bone...?!
Ｔボーン大佐までよくも…
Hey! Report this to CP9!
おい！ＣＰ９に報告だ！
There are still some lackeys?
まだ雑魚がいたか
Frites...
フリット…
Assorties!
アソルティ！
Sogeking...
そげキーング…
Gunpowder Star!
ガンパウダースター！
Strong Right!
ストロングライト！
Fire the heavyweight bullets!
重量弾　撃て！
They hit him!
うわっ！食らった！
Ow.
いて…
Fire! Fire!
撃て撃て！
How come the gun isn't working?!
何でピストルが効かねえんだ！？
H-Hey! What the hell are you?!
お…　おい！ お前一体何なんだ？
Oh, I'm a cyborg.
ああ…　俺はサイボーグなのよ
A cyborg?!
サイボーグ！？
Yep.
そう
Steel and weapons are built into my body.
体内に鋼鉄や兵器が仕込んである
If I'm shot, it hurts a bit, and I might bleed,
撃たれりゃ多少痛えし 血が出ることもあるが
but that's about it.
まあ　効きゃあしねえ
Something like that is possible?
そんなことがあんのか…
The world is a big place, huh?
世界は広いな
Amazing!
すげーっ！
So if I...
えいっ
Ouch!
痛え～っ！
What are you doing, you jerk?!
何してんだてめえ！
What? You felt that tiny needle?
えっ？ 針ぐらい効かねえんじゃねえのか？
You butthead!
このボケ！
Do I look like your science experiment?!
おっそろしい実験コーナーおっぱじめやがって
Fine, listen up! My back is different!
じゃあ　先に言っとくが背中は違う！
You see,
いいか？
because I did the modifications myself, I couldn't reach my back.
この改造は１人でやったからよ 後ろの面は届かなかったんだ
Only my front is cybernetic.
前半分だけがサイボーグだ！
Y'know, while I'm at it, I'll tell you one more thing.
じゃあもう１つついでに教えてやる
My belly tends to get chilly. Any clue why?
俺はおなかが冷え性 なぜでしょう？
How would I know?
知らねえよ
It's because I've got a fridge in my stomach to chill cola.
腹にコーラを冷やす 冷蔵庫がついてるからだ
Whoa! That's handy!
おっ！そりゃいいな！
Amazing! That'd be great on a scorcher!
すっげ～！暑い日最高だ！
Hey, this isn't the time for small talk!
…って言ってる場合かてめえら！
We beat all the enemies in this car!
もうこの車両敵いねえじゃねえか
It's clear, so let's move on!
クリアだ　次行くぞ！
Next up, car four.
次は第４車両
I'm Wanze!
ワンゼだよーん！
I'm mad, mad Wanze!
マッドなマッドなワンゼだよーん！
Now, now, now!
さっさっさっさっさ～っ
I'm Wanze!
ワンゼだよーん！
Hey, fellas!
おっすお前たち！
Are you hungry?
腹減ってる？
I'm Wanze.
俺はワンゼ
I'm the head steward, so I can cook anything!
給仕長だから何でも作れるよ
Want some ramen? Okay, I'll make ramen.
ラーメンにする？ じゃラーメンにするけど
But first, I wanna share a juicy tidbit with you.
その前に１つ知っといてほしい 豆知識があるんだよね
My nose hairs look like this!
俺の鼻毛はこう！
They reticulate, crisscrossing like fishnet pantyhose.
中で網状に 網タイツみたいになってるってことね
Keep that in mind!
これよく覚えといて！
Okay, then! First, I'll put the flour in my mouth and knead it well.
はい！まず小麦粉を口に含んで よ～くこねます
Now, bon appétit!
さあ　召し上がれ！
– Who'd eat that?!
–　いるかーっ！
Well, that was a waste of time.
時間を無駄にした
Wanze, we're keeping someone waiting.
ワンゼ 俺たちは人を待たせてる
We're in a hurry. So, see ya.
先を急ぐんで　じゃあな
Hold it!
待て～っ！
If you want to pass through this car,
この車両を通り抜けたければ
you'll have to go through me!
俺を倒してから進め！
Are you trying to stop us?
俺たちを止める気か？
I will stop you! Now, now, now, now!
止めるよ　ささっさっさーっ！
That's why I'm on this escort mission!
この海列車の護送任務
In the event of an attack like this, I'm here to handle it!
こういう万が一の襲撃のために 俺はいるんだよーっ！
If you want to free the criminal, you'll have to best my ramen kenpo!
罪人を解放したいんだったら この俺のラーメン拳法に勝ってみろ！
R-Ramen kenpo?!
ラ…　ラーメン拳法！？
"R-Ramen kenpo?!"
“ラ…　ラーメン拳法！？”
That son of a bitch! He's mocking me!
んにゃろう 人バカにしやがって！
Don't lose your cool, moron! That's what he wants!
乗せられんなバカ！思うツボだろ！
Now, now, now! How was my impersonation of that idiot?
さっさっさーっ！ どうだった？アホのモノマネ
Like I said, keep calm!
だから乗せられんなって
Now, now, now, now!
さっさっさっさーっ！
This guy needs a chill pill.
落ち着きのねえヤツめ
What?! The bullets grazed him,
ぐっ？何だ？ 弾がかすったってのに！
but he still looks unfazed. Carefree, even...
顔色一つ変えねえあの余裕…
I-I thought my heart was gonna jump out of my chest!
し…　臓が飛び出るかと思った
So you were shocked?!
驚いてたのかよ
Control your expressions, will you?!
ややこしい顔してんじゃねえ！
– I'll handle this pain in the ass!
–　あんなふざけた野郎は俺が…
Wait, you guys.
待て待て
If he can push your buttons that easily, we'll be here all night.
お前らみてえにあいつのペースに いちいち翻弄されてちゃ　時間を食うだけだ
I'll make short work of him.
俺が手っ取り早く片づけてやる
What really irks me is someone like you calling themselves a cook.
何が腹立たしいって てめえがそれで料理人と名乗ってやがることさ
I'm talking to you!
てめえに言ったんだよ！
– Hey! He got to you, too!
–　おめえが乗せられてんじゃねえか！
But look!
だが見ろ
He dodged Sanji's kick easily!
サンジの蹴りを軽くかわした！
What's with his carefree expression?!
何だあの余裕の表情…
I thought I was a goner!
死ぬかと思った
So you were shocked?!
驚いてたのかよ！
I'm over this gag!
やめんか　そのパターン！
Anyway...
とにかく…
leave this guy to me.
こいつは俺に任せて
You guys go to the next car.
お前ら　次の車両へ行け
The rear two cars were detached?
後部２車両切り離された？
What are you people doing back there?
あなたたち一体何やってるの
We apologize profusely.
申し訳ありません！
One of our heavy hitters, Captain T-Bone, was in the detached cars as well.
強力な戦力Ｔボーン大佐まで 切り離されてしまったしだいで…
Fine, bring me up to speed on the situation.
で… 今の列車内の状況は？
Yes, ma'am!
はい！
There are five cars remaining, excluding the locomotive.
ただいま残っているのは 機関車両の他に全部で５車両です
However, every soldier in car five has been wiped out.
しかし第５車両の兵士は全員のされ
So that only leaves Agent Wanze in car four,
残っているのは第４車両のワンゼ氏
Agent Nero in car three,
そして第３車両のネロ氏
Nico Robin in car one,
あとは第１車両のニコ･ロビンと
and everyone here in car two!
この第２車両の皆さんのみとなっています
It would seem our enemy is no fool.
敵もバカじゃなさそうだな
However, if there is a problem here for us,
だが　事実上 こっちに不都合があるとすれば
it's only the fact that Franky is loose.
フランキーが自由の身であることだけだ
Our mission is to bring Franky and Nico Robin to Enies Lobby, nothing more.
我々の任務はフランキーとニコ･ロビンの２人を エニエス･ロビーへ届けることのみ
Besides that, regardless of how the other enemies die,
それ以外はヤツらの誰がどうくたばろうと
or if our own allies should fall,
こっちサイドの誰がどうなろうと
it won't interfere with our mission.
任務に支障はない
Well, did you catch a glimpse of the enemy?
それで敵の姿は見たの？
Yes, ma'am! First, there were the two that were in custody,
ええ まずは捕まっていた例の２人
although one of them was wearing a bizarre mask.
１人は妙な仮面着けていましたが…
There was also a dapper blond we've never seen before!
それと 見たことのない金髪のスーツ男の
So, a total of three!
計３人です！
Just like the long-nosed man, that man is probably one of the Straw Hats.
そいつは長鼻の男と同様 麦わらの仲間じゃろうな
Naturally, his purpose is to recover Nico Robin.
目的は当然ニコ･ロビンの奪回
Looks like Franky is assisting them.
フランキーはその手伝いというところか…
Lucci, shall I go stand watch over Nico Robin?
ルッチ 俺がニコ･ロビンを見張っていようか？
That's not necessary.
必要ない
Focus on recapturing Franky.
フランキーをもう一度捕まえることだけ考えろ
They can try as they might to rescue Nico Robin...
ニコ･ロビンを取り返すことなど
but in the end, their efforts...
あいつらには
will all be for naught.
絶対できない
I... won't... let... you... pass... through!
行･か･せ･な･い･よ～！
I'll knead alloy flour and...!
合金小麦粉こねて！
Is he gonna bring out ramen again?!
またラーメン出す気か？
Ramen...
ラーメン…
Beam...!
ビーム
Those are sharp!
刺さる！
Yikes!
危ねえ！
Knock it off!
やめろ～っ！
Oopsie!
ちょいや！
Let's go up and around!
上から回るぞ
Yeah!
んっああ
W-Well then, Sir Sanji! Best of luck to you!
で…　ではサンジ君 頑張りたまえ
Now, now, now, now!
さっさっさっさーっ！
They got away so easily!
あっさり逃げられた
But it doesn't matter!
でも　それも無駄だよ
Nero is waiting for them in the next car!
だって 次の車両に控えているのは　ネロだ！
He may be the newbie, but he's an agent of CP9, a group of assassins for justice! They're toast!
新入りとはいえ正義の殺し屋ＣＰ９ あいつら死ぬよ
Nero loves to kill! Now, now, now, now!
ネロは殺しが大好きなのさ！ さっさっさっさーっ！
Flanchet...
フランシェ…
Shoot!
シュート！
How many times do I need to say it? I'm in a hurry.
急いでると何度も言わすな
In that case, take this!
んじゃあいくぞ
Ramen Kenpo: Noodle Slicer!
ラーメン拳法　麺切り！
Fire...
ファイア…
Skate!
スケート！
Ow, ow, ow...!
いてて…
He dodged while also kicking me, like, ten times!
かわされた瞬間に 10発くらい蹴られた～っ！
Twelve times, actually.
12発だ
Is it possible... that you're super strong?
お前　まさか めちゃめちゃ強いんじゃない？
You're just not as strong as you think.
お前が口ほどにもねえだけだろ
Hey, hey!
おいおい！
Not even my old man talks to me like that!
口ほどにもねえなんて オヤジにも言われたことねえよ！
Quit being so rude!
やめろ！失敬な！
I'm Wanze!
俺はワンゼだよーん！
You know what? You're actually pretty good!
実際　俺がお前の珍しい グルグル眉毛によって
Even if I am getting dizzy looking at your weird eyebrows.
目　回してたとこ 差し引いても　お前なかなかやるな！
You're one to talk about someone's face being weird!
お前に顔が珍しいとか言われたくねえよ！
Okay, then!
よし　いいよ！
I'll show you why I was chosen for the criminal escort team!
俺がなぜ　この罪人護送チームに 選ばれたかは　今すぐお前に分からせてやる
Ramen Kenpo Secret Technique...
ラーメン拳法　奥義！
Beat the noodles! Beat the noodles, and they're done!
麺を鍛えて　麺を鍛えて 出来上がる…
Wha...?
なっ…
What the hell is this?
何だこりゃ？
The edible combat suit of your dreams!
食べられる　夢の戦闘服
Ra-Men's Formal Suit!
麺ズフォーマルスーツ！
Now, now, now!
さっさっさーっ！
The real trick to ramen kenpo is controlling the noodles at will!
ラーメン拳法の極意は 麺を自由自在に操ることにある
You bastard...
この…
How dare you keep playing with food?!
さっきから食い物で遊びやがって
Speed, power, and special abilities...
スピード　パワー　特殊能力…
in all those areas, I'm on a whole other level now!
全てがさっきまでの俺とは違う！
I'll show you incomparable strength!
桁違いの強さを発揮するよーん！
Enough talk. Bring it.
しゃべりはいいから かかってこい
I hope you're hungry, because I'm gonna make you eat every last one of those damn noodles.
てめえ その麺全部食わせてやるから覚悟しろ
So...
で？
who the hell are you?
何なのよおめえは？
Waiting atop car three is CP9's newbie,
第３車両に控えますは
a Four Powers master,
四式使いＣＰ９の新入り
Nero the Sea Weasel.
海イタチのネロ
But what a shame, you're someone I can't kill...
しかし　何だ… あんたじゃ殺すわけにゃいかないねえ
since you're one of our important criminals.
大切な罪人だもんねえ
Hey, buddy!
おう　お兄ちゃん
Why are you out on the roof?
何でこんな屋根の上に出てきてんのよ
If you had just waited, I would've come to you.
待ってりゃ俺から行くところを…
Well, that wasn't a certainty, right?
そりゃ分かんないっしょ
You might've cheated and skipped this car, right?
ズルして飛び越えてたかもしれねえっしょ
You're pretty vigilant!
ずいぶん用心深いこった
But being on guard is important, huh?
しかしまあ 警戒は大事だよなあ
By the way, what's that behind you?
それより おめえの後ろにあるそれ　何だ？
That was scummy!
汚えぞ！
Hell yeah it was!
結構
Back home, I'm the king of the scum.
町じゃ悪党の親玉でね
Octoshoes...
オクトパクツ…
Long Nose!
長鼻君！？
Why are you here?!
どうしてここに？
♪ Sniper–
そげ…